== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Penny:)Okay, I'm gonna go pick up
my family.
(Penny:)Like an hour and half,
two hours, depending on traffic.
(Leonard:)Yeah, drive safe.
Oh, hey,
and do yourself a favor,
all right?
(Penny:)When Beverly gets here,
do not bring up last night.
(Penny:)All right?
As far as you're concerned,
(Penny:)you don't know anything,
(Penny:)you didn't see anything.
(Penny:)I want you just to play dumb.
(Sheldon:)It was nice of her to show us
playing dumb with an example.
(Leonard:)What?
(Penny:)Oh.
(Penny:)Hi. Okay, hey there, I got--
I'm sorry, I got to go now.
(Beverley:)Penny, wait.
Why?
(Beverley:)I wanted to thank you for
going through all the trouble
(Beverley:)of planning a second wedding
ceremony for me,
(Beverley:)but unfortunately
I cannot attend.
(Leonard:)Well, why?
What's wrong?
Wha-- are we still doing
the dumb thing?
(Sheldon:)Okay, why, what's wrong?
(Beverley:)I just cannot stay here
while your father
(Beverley:)goes out of his way
to humiliate me.
(Sheldon:)Oh, golly, however
did he humiliate you?
(Beverley:)Stop it, Sheldon.